loansable.com 2018-04-19

# Privacy Policy – Loans Able

#### Privacy Policy of Loans Able

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Loans Able, we have a few fundamental principles:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)  
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the ongoing operation of one of our services.  
In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.  
Below is our privacy policy, which incorporates these goals.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact us.

Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Loans Able collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Loans Able’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Loans Able’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Loans Able may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Loans Able also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. Loans Able only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Loans Able’s websites choose to interact with Loans Able in ways that require Loans Able to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Loans Able gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at WordPress.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Loans Able – by purchasing access to the Akismet comment spam prevention service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Loans Able collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Loans Able. Loans Able does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

Loans Able may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Loans Able may monitor the most popular blogs on the WordPress.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Loans Able may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Loans Able does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Loans Able discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Loans Able’s behalf or to provide services available at Loans Able’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Loans Able’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Loans Able will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Loans Able discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Loans Able believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Loans Able, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Loans Able website and have supplied your email address, Loans Able may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Loans Able and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Loans Able takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Loans Able uses cookies to help Loans Able identify and track visitors, their usage of Loans Able website, and their website access preferences. Loans Able visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Loans Able’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Loans Able’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Business Transfers

If Loans Able, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Loans Able goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Loans Able may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Loans Able and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Comments

Comments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives or missed spam, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives and missed spam.
